[
        {
                "question": "Я сделяю это",
                "answer": "I'll do it"
        },
        {
                "question": "Мы минимизируем расходы",
                "answer": "We'll minimize the costs"
        },
        {
                "question": "Ты устанешь скоро",
                "answer": "You'll get tired soon"
        },
        {
                "question": "они максимизируют прибыль",
                "answer": "They'll maximize the profit"
        },
        {
                "question": "У него будет свободное время",
                "answer": "He'll have free time"
        },
        {
                "question": "Она будет манипулировать этим",
                "answer": "She'll manipulate it"
        },
        {
                "question": "Это будет стимулировать их",
                "answer": "It'll stimulate them"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я достигну этой цели",
                "answer": "I'll achieve this aim"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я буду говорить по английски вовсе без каких-либо ошибок",
                "answer": "I'll speak english without any mistakes at all"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я скажу это снова",
                "answer": "I'll say it again"
        },
        {
                "question": "я найду новую работу",
                "answer": "I'll look for a new job"
        },
        {
                "question": "я скажу ему об этой проблеме",
                "answer": "I'll tell him about this problem"
        },
        {
                "question": "Мы обдумаем это",
                "answer": "We'll think it over"
        },
        {
                "question": "Мы будем счастливы",
                "answer": "We'll be happy"
        },
        {
                "question": "Мы скоро пойдем в отпуск",
                "answer": "We'll go on holiday soon"
        },
        {
                "question": "Мы будем благодарны тебе за это",
                "answer": "We'll be grateful to you for it"
        },
        {
                "question": "Мы сэкономим немного денег",
                "answer": "We'll save some money"
        },
        {
                "question": "Ты потратишь меньше денег",
                "answer": "You'll spend less money"
        },
        {
                "question": "Ты будешь удовлетворен своим результатом",
                "answer": "You'll be satisfied with your result"
        },
        {
                "question": "Они объяснят это нам",
                "answer": "They'll explain it to us"
        },
        {
                "question": "У них будет выбор",
                "answer": "They'll have a choise"
        },
        {
                "question": "У них будет другая альтернатива",
                "answer": "They'll have an another alternative"
        },
        {
                "question": "Они скоро поженятся",
                "answer": "They'll get married soon"
        },
        {
                "question": "это тебя шокирует",
                "answer": "It'll shock you"
        },
        {
                "question": "Это очень сильно удивит тебя",
                "answer": "It'll surprise you greatly"
        },
        {
                "question": "Это изменит твою точку зрения",
                "answer": "It'll change your point of view"
        },
        {
                "question": "это будет зависеть от других факторов",
                "answer": "It'll depend on other factors"
        },
        {
                "question": "рано или поздно это произойдет",
                "answer": "It'll happen sooner or later"
        }
]
